jasonheiglfoundation.org 2017-02-27

# Privacy Policy | The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation

### Policy Effective As Of August 19, 2011

The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation, a 501(c)3 non-profit organization ("Jason Debus Heigl Foundation", "JDHF", "we" or "us"), which has adopted a set of Privacy Terms (the "Terms"). The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation has implemented those terms in this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy"), which describes how we collect, use and share personal information ( "PI") we obtain online from and about individuals located in the U.S.:

The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation’s web site ([http://jasonheigl.foundation](http://jasonheigl.foundation/)) and all other related web sites owned or controlled by us (collectively or individually the "Site") are general audience web sites, and we do not knowingly collect PI from children under 13 years of age.

Our Privacy Policy applies to "Visitors," which means that you simply browse the Site and to "volunteer, adoption, or fostering candidates" ("Candidate" or "you") which means that you have registered with the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation. The term "User" refers to a Visitor or Candidate. By using our Site, you signify your agreement with all the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site.

From time to time the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, our PI collection and use practices, the features of our Site or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PI, the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation will post those changes in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of such Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site after the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date with our most current policies and practices.

If the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PI, your PI will continue to be governed by the Privacy Policy under which it has been collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change. In the event the last e-mail address you provided to us is not valid or is not capable of delivering the notice to you, the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation’s dispatch of an e-mail containing the notice to that e-mail address shall nonetheless constitute effective notice.

### A. Collection Of PI By The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation

1\. General. When the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation collects PI, such as your full name, email address and/or phone number, from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting PI to us in order to register as a candidate or because you want us to furnish you with services or information. We may also obtain PI from reputable third parties.

Candidates can change their Registration Data (as defined below in Section A(1)a) at any time and can control how the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation communicates with them.

The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation collects information from you at several different points on the Site in the manner set forth below.

(a). Candidate Registration:

In order to access certain information and services on the Site, you must first become a Candidate by completing one of our forms. During the registration process you will be required to provide registration data, which may include PI such as your name and e-mail address (such information is the "Registration Data").

(b). Information and Site Updates:

Unless a User has opted out of receiving such e-mails during the registration process, the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation may occasionally send Users who provide us with their e-mail addresses information about, Site updates and other offerings via e-mail. We may also send information about offerings of our partners that we think may be of interest to our users. To opt out of receiving these e-mails from us please contact the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation as provided below.

2\. Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that the Site places on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on our Site and enable the Jason Debus Heigl Foundation to make your visits to our Site more enjoyable. Information about your activities on our Site and other non-PI about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.

Third party advertisements displayed on our Site may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. The Jason Debus Heigl Foundation does not control these cookies and visitors to our Site should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. Please refer to Section B below for more information on third party advertisements.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies you may not have access to certain features on our Site.

Pages: 1 [2](http://jasonheigl.foundation/privacy-policy/2/) [3](http://jasonheigl.foundation/privacy-policy/3/)
